Innovations Through Technology UP241
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Innovations Through Technology
2002 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Media Enterprises
Academic Technology Services
University Information Technology
UP241
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Innovations through Technology. It includes articles to help schools and faculty to integrate technology into their educational and research objectives. It supports the mandate of Academic Technology (AT), a university-wide resource that provides guidance and professional advice on using instructional technology in support of teaching and research initiatives. Originally published as Innovations in Learning, Newsletter of Academic Technology in September 2002. The name changed to Innovations through Technology in December 2006.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Media Enterprises was organized in 2002 to take over various university publications including the Tufts Health Letter, Your Dog, Catnip and Healthy Living as well as single run publications of various books.
- Innovations through Technology, 2002 -- 2012; UP241.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This collection contains Innovations through Technology. It includes articles to help schools and faculty to integrate technology into their educational and research objectives. It supports the mandate of Academic Technology (AT), a university-wide resource that provides guidance and professional advice on using instructional technology in support of teaching and research initiatives. Originally published as Innovations in Learning, Newsletter of Academic Technology in September 2002. The name changed to Innovations through Technology in December 2006.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Innovations in Learning, 2002-09; UP241.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Academic Technology
  - Innovations in Learning, 2002-11; UP241.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2003-02; UP241.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2003-04; UP241.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2003-09; UP241.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2003-11; UP241.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2004-03; UP241.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2004-06; UP241.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2004-09; UP241.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2004-11; UP241.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Innovations in Learning, 2005-03; UP241.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2006-12; UP241.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2007-02; UP241.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2007-05; UP241.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2007-09; UP241.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2007-11; UP241.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2008-03; UP241.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2008-05; UP241.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2008-09; UP241.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, 2009-10; UP241.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, Fall, 2011; UP241.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, Winter, 2012; UP241.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Innovations through Technology, Spring, 2012; UP241.001.001.00023 (Box 1)